Shajahan

Contact

91+8870898546



shajahanshaji0808@gmail.com



11,L.N.Puram,Aranthangi ,Pudukkottai,TamilNadu 614616



Education

(2010-2011)SSLC - 52%

Government Boys Higher Secondary School – Aranthangi.

(2012-2013)Hsc - 56%

Government Boys Higher
Secondary School – Aranthangi.

(2015-2018) B.Sc (CS) -71%,

Graduated Bharathidasan University Model college – Aranthangi

key skills

Microsoft Office

Tamil and English

Web and tech savvy

Typing speed of 40 WPM

Problem solving

Team leadership

Profile

Administrative Assistant with 2.5+ years of experience entering customer data and account data from source documents within time limits. Compiling, verifying accuracy and sorting information to prepare source data for computer entry. Reviewing data for deficiencies or errors, correction any incompatibilities and checking output.

Contacting potential or existing customers to inform about a product or service using scripts. Answering question about products or the company. Asking questions to understand customer requirements and close sales.

professional experience

(June 2018 - November 2020)

Jio Networks Department SS Agencies – Aranthangi.

- Compiling, verifying accuracy and sorting Information to prepare source data for computer entry. Reviewing data deficiencies or errors.
- Trained 2 administrative assistants during a period of company expansion to ensure attention to detail and adherence to company
- Handle Incoming requests from customers to ensure prompt of the queries resulting In complete satisfaction and acceptance. communicate effectively and professionally with Internal external customers to resolve questions and Issues.
- Check If you have plan with validity and data balance on your Jio number. Check If your mobile phone Is compatible with Jio 4G. Ensure your network settings on your device are enabled. Ensure that you have completed the tele-verification process.
- Manage travel and expense reports for department team members

(August 2021 - February 2022)

Executive

Asirvat Microfinance – Aranthangi.

- Type documents such as correspondence, drafts, memos, and emails, and prepared 3 reports daily for management
- Responsible for a business's money transactions, Including Income andf expenses a finance executive makes sure that their organization Is profitable the manage cash-flow statements, budgeting and tac planning. They also determines ways of the company to cut costs to maximize profits.
- Purchased and maintained office suppled inventories, and always carefully adhered to budgeting practices
- Greeted visitors and helped them either find the appropriate person or schedule an appointment